Serhii Vernyhora lereilemie@gmail.com

Software engineer who has 5 years Frontend, 3 years Backend experiences with demonstrated hands-on experience in strengthen Web Application and Hybrid mobile App development, and 3 years experience of Smart Contract and Web3 engineer.

SUMMARY

Experienced JavaScript Developer in web and Mobile (React Native) development with a demonstrated history in IT industry and various works. Skilled in React, Angular, Vue, Svelte frontend technology, and Node.js, Python, PHP backend technology, and have in-depth and wide-ranged knowledge of Blockchain technology - Smart Contract development on Ethereum and Solana network as well. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science and Programming.

LANGUAGES

JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Node, Next, React, Vue, Angular, Svelte, Python, PHP, SQL, GraphQL, React Native, Expo, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Django, AWS, Firebase, Solidity, Web3, Golang, Rust

WORK EXPERIENCE

eGroupTeam [Lead Frontend Developer]

Taipei-Taiwan [2022/10 - Present]

Responsibility

- > Contributing to Building React Component **Library** & Updating **NPM pkgs** for company business with **React.JS**(using MUI react-library), **TypeScript**, **Storybook** library (<u>eGroupTeam/egroup-material</u>)
- ➤ Business management/Assistant CRM website frontend Development/Maintenance, and API integration Next.JS, Typescript (eGroupAI.com)
- > Responsible for **Optimizing** functional **UI Components** and **Performance** of website, **Efficiency** in business operation and management has been **significantly** increased by more than **70%**.
- > Responsible for **Testing** functional UI components and system structure **Unit Test, Integration Test**
- > Responsible in **Technical guide** for other developers, and **Code review** of their result as a frontend development leader.
- > Constructing of Scalable System with continuous Integration of new UI Features with New Web Technology that benefits the business.

SigmaOffice [Blockchain/Web3 Developer]

Sydney-Australia [2021/10 - 2022/09]

Responsibility

- ➤ Internship with learning **Blockchain** technology and **Web3.JS**
- > Building auto Trading bot platform using React.js + Typescript and TailwindCSS. winbee
- > Integrating Smart-contract and web3.is for withdraw & Deposit logic.

Freelancer [React Native Hybrid Mobile Developer]

Freelancing [2020/04 - 2021/09]

- ➤ Mobile App for Android and iOS **Node.js** backend, **React.js** web portal, **Mongodb**, Push notification alert for QR code scanning of a delivering package (**GlobeForward**)
- Real-time location tracking mobile application development with Firebase backend integration and mobile sensors –
 Geolocation Service, Firebase, Expo (Seguros)

ITPackPro [Web Developer – Freelancing]

USA [2017/03 - 2020/03]

- > Web developer in large scale web application, converted platform from PHP to React.js of Healthcare Web App.
- Node.js backend engineering and frontend developer experience in JavaScript technology in various web application development. (TypeScript, React.js, Angular.js, Vue.js, Node.js, Mongodb, Mapbox, AWS EC2/S3)

EDUCATION